{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4938","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4938","name":"UFO Factory","address":"2110  Trumbull","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Aliccia Bolling-Fisher","licenseNumber":"081268","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Plan Review","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.06697,42.33217","geojson":{"id":"4938","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.066970846,42.332167028]},"properties":{"name":"UFO Factory","owner":"Aliccia Bolling-Fisher","address":"2110  Trumbull","zipcode":"48207","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"081268","establishmentid":"4938","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Plan Review","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"30/3/2022"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51623349","name":"Momento Gelato And Coffee","address":"2120 Trumbull","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51622941","name":"Michigan & Trumbull","address":"1441 Elizabeth","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"500","name":"McShane's","address":"1460 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"4105","name":"Onassis Coney Island","address":"1501 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4648","name":"Ottava Via","address":"1400 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1409","name":"Manna Meals","address":"1950 Trumbull","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"545","name":"Nemos","address":"1378 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51623947","name":"Godfrey Hotel Det 7th Floor Bar & Pantry","address":"1401 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51623948","name":"Godfrey Hotel-The Hamilton @ Godfrey","address":"1401 Michigan","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"51623946","name":"Godfrey Hotel Det. Lobby Bar & Banquets","address":"1401 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48216"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60606","inspectionDate":"2022-10-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On top of the Stove","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"56401","inspectionDate":"2021-10-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Light fixture","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"52902","inspectionDate":"2020-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Digital Thermometer","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"PATIO","subLocation":"At the Ice scoop","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."},{"violationCode":"6-501.16","violationDescription":"After use, mops shall be placed in a position that allows them to air-dry without soiling walls, EQUIPMENT, or supplies.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wet mop(s) storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly dried","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the Mop","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Allow to air dry in an approved location."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (upright)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"52903","inspectionDate":"2020-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Outdoor cafe Eval","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49431","inspectionDate":"2019-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"Food","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Under the Popcorn machine","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44231","inspectionDate":"2018-10-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"39168","inspectionDate":"2017-07-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Under the Bar","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4938"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}